const qBank = [
  {
    question:
      "How many chapters are there in the Holy Quran?   ",
    answers: ["112", "114", "666", "662"],
    correct: "114",
    questionId: "099099"
  },
  {
    question:
      'Where was the Holy Prophet Muhammad SAW born?',
    answers: ["Mecca", "Madina", "Czech Republic", "Dubai"],
    correct: "Mecca",
    questionId: "183452"
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the first battle fought in Islam?",
    answers: ["Badr", "Uhud", "World-war 2", "khandar"],
    correct: "HTC",
    questionId: "Badr"
  },
  {
    question: "What's the name of the Holy prophet's parents?",
    answers: [
      "Abdullahi & Amina",
      "Abdullah & Ummulkhair",
      "Musa & Amina",
      "Abbas & Suwaiba"
    ],
    correct: "Abdullahi & Amina",
    questionId: "333247"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the most common name in the world?",
    answers: ["Umma", "Muhammad", "John", "Evans"],
    correct: "Muhammad",
    questionId: "496293"
  },
  {
    question:
      "which scripture was revealed to prophet Musa (AS)?",
    answers: [
      "Zabur",
      "Taurah",
      "Oxford dictionary",
      "Ingeel"
    ],
    correct: "Ingeel",
    questionId: "588909"
  },
  {
    question:
      'Who was the first caliph after the death of the prophet Muhammad (PBUH)?',
    answers: ["Abu bakr", "Peter", "Mufti Menk", "Umar Bn Khattab"],
    correct: "Abu bakr",
    questionId: "648452"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the first book of the Old Testament?",
    answers: ["Genesis", "Exodus", "Leviticus", "Numbers"],
    correct: "Genesis",
    questionId: "786649"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which of the companions did the prophet Muhammad (PBUH) enjoin the responsibility of the adhan?",
    answers: ["Bilal ibn Rabah", "None of the above", "Abdur-Rahman Sudais", "Abdullah Bn Masood"],
    correct: "Bilal ibn Rabah",
    questionId: "839754"
  },
  {
    question:
      "who is the fourth of the rightly guided Caliph after the life of Prophet Muhammad(PBUH)?",
    answers: [
      "Ibn Taimiyyah",
      "Uthman Bn Affan",
      "Sheikh Jafar",
      "Ali Bn Abu Talib"
    ],
    correct: "Ali Bn Abu Talib",
    questionId: "98390"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the first matyr in islam?",
    answers: ["Khadija", "Sumayya", "Balls", "Fatima"],
    correct: "Sumayya",
    questionId: "1071006"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the third month of of the islamic calender?",
    answers: ["Rabiul sani", "Rabiul Awwal", "Jumada Awwal", "March"],
    correct: "Rabiul Awwal",
    questionId: "1174154"
  },
  {
    question: "Area 51 is located in which US state?",
    answers: ["Nevada", "Arizona", "New Mexico", "Utah"],
    correct: "Nevada",
    questionId: "1226535"
  },
  {
    question: "How would one say goodbye in Spanish?",
    answers: ["Adiós", " Hola", "Au Revoir", "Salir"],
    correct: "Adiós",
    questionId: "1310938"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of tribe of our Holy Prophet?",
    answers: ["Quraysh", "Arabian", "Hashim", "Kanuri"],
    correct: "Quraysh",
    questionId: "1436873"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the Prophet nurse?",
    answers: ["Halimatus Saadiya", "Ummulkhair", "Ummu Salma", "Nurse Zahra"],
    correct: "Halimatus Saadiya",
    questionId: "1515110"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the second battle in islam?",
    answers: ["Badr", "Cold War", "civil War", "Uhud"],
    correct: "Uhud",
    questionId: "1642728"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is the first man to accept islam? ",
    answers: ["Muhammadu Buhari", "Ali Bn Abu Talib", "Abu Bakr", "Usman Danfodio"],
    correct: "Abu Bakr",
    questionId: "1747256"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who si the first woman to accept islam?",
    answers: ["Maryam Lemu", "Khadija", "Aisha", "Queen Amina"],
    correct: "Khadija",
    questionId: "1822532"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the first slave to accept islam?",
    answers: [
      "Malcom X",
      "Bilal Bn Rabah",
      "Abraham Lincoln",
      "Zayd"
    ],
    correct: "Zayd",
    questionId: "195075"
  },
  {
    question: 'which African country did some group of Sahabas migrated to during Prophet time?',
    answers: ["Mauritania", "Ethopia", "Egypt", "Nigeria"],
    correct: "Ethopia",
    questionId: "2019778"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the Jewish New Year?",
    answers: ["Rosh Hashanah", "Elul", "New Year", "Succoss"],
    correct: "Rosh Hashanah",
    questionId: "2134343"
  },
  {
    question: "Who was the king of Habash when Muslims migrated there?",
    answers: [
      "Ado Bayero",
      "Najashi",
      "Aalafin Oyo",
      "Fahad"
    ],
    correct: "Najashi",
    questionId: "2210799"
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the name of the Sahab that represented the group of muslims that migrated to Africa?",
    answers: ["Nasir Albani", "Jafar Bn Abu Talib", "Umar Abdul Azeez", "Ali Bn Abu Talib"],
    correct: "Jafar Bn Abu Talib",
    questionId: "2379831"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the Animal that the Prophet rode on his journey to heaven?",
    answers: ["Shrek", "Buraq", "Wave Rider", "Dragon"],
    correct: "Buraq",
    questionId: "2426418"
  },
  {
    question: "Which Surah is called the heart of the Quran?",
    answers: ["Ikhlas", "Baqarah", "Yasin", "Al Fatiha"],
    correct: "Yasin",
    questionId: "2510086"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the cave where revelation of Holy Qyran started?",
    answers: [
      "Cave of Hira",
      "Cave of Mayan",
      "Zuma rock",
      "Cave of Thawr"
    ],
    correct: "Cave of Hira",
    questionId: "2685745"
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the old name of of Madinatul Munawwarah?",
    answers: ["Adis Ababa", "Yathrib", "Zaria", "Cairo"],
    correct: "Yathrib",
    questionId: "2796884"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the village the Prophet mother was buried?",
    answers: ["Nairobi", "Tokyo", "Riyaad", "Abwaab"],
    correct: "Abwaab",
    questionId: "2838900"
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following is not a source of Shariah(Islamic Law)?',
    answers: ["Sunnah", "Quran", " Qiyas", "Fatwa"],
    correct: "Fatwa",
    questionId: "298060"
  },
  {
    question: "which of the following is the largest Muslim country in the world by population?",
    answers: ["Syria", "Saudi Arabia", "Iran", "Indonesia"],
    correct: "Indonesia",
    questionId: "3096579"
  },
  {
    question: "how many prophets were mentioned in the holy Quran?",
    answers: [
      "20",
      "25",
      "30",
      "35"
    ],
    correct: "25",
    questionId: "3182461"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the name of the longest chapter in holy Quran?",
    answers: [
      "Anfaal",
      "Genesis",
      "Baqarah",
      "Al Imraan"
    ],
    correct: "Baqarah",
    questionId: "3239112"
  },
  {
    question: "how many verses are there in the holy Quran?",
    answers: ["6326", "6236", "6790", "6666"],
    correct: "6236",
    questionId: "3318503"
  },
  {
    question:
      'What is the name of the shortest chapter in the holy Quran',
    answers: ["Al Fatiha", "Nas", "Ikhlas", "Al Kawthar"],
    correct: "Al Kawthar",
    questionId: "3410327"
  },
  {
    question: "How many words are there in the Holy Quran?",
    answers: ["98000", "67000", "89000", "79000"],
    correct: "79000",
    questionId: "3542596"
  },
  {
    question: "how many letters are there in the Holy Quran",
    answers: ["312839", "343890", "323670", "329000"],
    correct: "323670",
    questionId: "3667517"
  },
  {
    question: "Who introduced the islamic calender?",
    answers: [
      "Umar Bn Khattab",
      "Ibn Qayyum",
      "Abubakar Gumi",
      "Uthman Bn Affaan"
    ],
    correct: "Umar Bn Khattab",
    questionId: "3791672"
  },
  {
    question: "Who built the first islamic navy?",
    answers: ["Usman DanFodio", "Shehu Inyas", "Abu Bakr", "Uthman Bn Affaan"],
    correct: "Uthman Bn Affaan",
    questionId: "3893585"
  },
  {
    question: 'Give one Arabic word for the unity of Allah?',
    answers: ["Seerah", "Tajweed", "Ikhlas", "Tawheed"],
    correct: "Tawheed",
    questionId: "3913430"
  },
  {
    question: "How tall is the Burj Khalifa?",
    answers: ["2,722 ft", "2,717 ft", "2,546 ft", "3,024 ft"],
    correct: "2,722 ft",
    questionId: "4049121"
  },
  {
    question:
      "Whic is the term for breaking of the fast?",
    answers: ["Uno", "Kareem", "Sahoor", "Iftar"],
    correct: "Iftar",
    questionId: "4150746"
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the number of Makki surahs in Quran?",
    answers: ["90", "91", "98", "93"],
    correct: "93",
    questionId: "4235063"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the number of madani surahs in Quran?",
    answers: ["22", "27", "21", "24"],
    correct: "21",
    questionId: "4321002"
  },
  {
    question: "What will be the spoken language in paradise?",
    answers: [
      "Hausa",
      "Arabic",
      "Spanish",
      "Hebrew"
    ],
    correct: "Arabic",
    questionId: "4442286"
  },
  {
    question: "How many letters are there in Arabic Language?",
    answers: [
      "29",
      "28",
      "27",
      "30"
    ],
    correct: "29",
    questionId: "4564430"
  },
  {
    question: "Value of salat in MAsjidil Aqsa?",
    answers: ["200", "1000", "500", "600"],
    correct: "500",
    questionId: "4630606"
  },
  {
    question:
      "How many letters have dots around them?",
    answers: ["20", "35", "25", "15"],
    correct: "15",
    questionId: "4795960"
  },
  {
    question: "How many letters do not have dots around them?",
    answers: ["24", "13", "33", "23"],
    correct: "13",
    questionId: "4811162"
  },
  {
    question: "What is the first month of the Islamic calender?",
    answers: ["Safar", "January", "Muharram", "Shawwal"],
    correct: "Muharram",
    questionId: "4982981"
  }
];

export default (n = 5) =>
  Promise.resolve(qBank.sort(() => 0.5 - Math.random()).slice(0, n));
